emiprotechnologies.com 2018-08-14

# Privacy Policy | Emipro Technologies Pvt Ltd | Emipro Technologies Private Limited

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. We request you to read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the terms and conditions described in this privacy policy. The terms and conditions mentioned in this policy may be changed, but any such changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retrospective basis. We encourage you to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

### Privacy statement 

We fully respect your right to privacy. This policy outlines what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also includes and describes other important topics related to your privacy. 

### Information Collection 

We will only collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through our website or e-mail correspondence. We may collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to improve our website and better meet your needs. 

### Use of Information 

Before collecting any personally identifiable information, we will provide an explanation for the possible use of the data that is being provided to us by you. The information you supply will be used by us in various ways such as to fulfill your orders for our products and services, respond to your inquiries, supply you with requested information the products and services etc. We may also use the information to inform you about new features, products or services if you explicitly instructed us to do so. 

### Distribution of Information 

We may share information with judicial/governmental/law enforcement agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: Permitted or required by law. Trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions. Investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information **will never be provided to any company for marketing purposes.**

### Commitment to Data Security 

All of your personally identifiable information is kept fully secure. Only authorized employees who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

### Cookie/Tracking Technology 

Some of our Web pages may contain "cookies," which are data that may be sent to your Web browser and stored on your computer. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. This allows our server to "recognize" you when you visit our Web site in the future. Most Web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you. 

### Privacy Contact Information 

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us on [ info@emiprotechnologies.com ](mailto:support@emiprotechnologies.com) . We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications on our site.
